But I mean, the original reason that they didn't give universe, create universal health care in black in America was because they didn't want black people to get it.
Oh, no, I did not know that part because it was on the table.
And then they were like, yeah, but then black people will get universal health care.
And we don't want black people to get universal health care.
Like now that they're not slaves anymore, they don't even serve a purpose here.
So if we make it so that they can't get universal health care, then they'll just die off and we'll get the country back to just being white people and doing whatever we want to do.
And basically that just didn't happen.
And it has continued to be pervasive.
You know, when we saw Obama and his Obamacare whole thing and people trying to act like, well, I won't be able to choose my doctor.
And it's like, but that's not true.
Like you will be like how many times we have to tell you that you can choose your doctor if you just stop saying that you can't choose your doctor.
It's really all about this idea that only certain people should have access to health care.
Now you have me thinking, I want to know because I know it's nearly like 300,000 Alabamians that don't have health care insurance like that don't have it at all.
But I wonder like what percentage of that are like black individuals.